evaluesoftware.com 2016-03-26

# Policies

## Collection of Personal Information

When placing an order at SoftwareSituation.com, you will be asked to submit personal information such as your name, address, email address, phone number, credit card or debit card information. This information is used to process and complete your order. Additionally, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and time of access. Your information is collected for the sole purpose of processing your order. Your information is not shared with outside parties except that which is necessary to process and complete the order, e.g. credit card verification, order shipment.

## Security

We have appropriate electronic, physical and management policies to secure and safeguard your information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and protected. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just "surfing".

## Business Operations, Law Enforcement and Legal Actions

We may release your information without prior notice when we believe it is appropriate to prevent fraud; to comply with law or to cooperate with law enforcement activity or other governmental request; to respond to subpoenas, court orders or administrative agency requests for information; to enforce our policies; to protect the rights, property and safety of our business and of others; or when required or otherwise permitted by law. For example, we may share information with law enforcement if we reasonably believe that someone is using or attempting to use our site for illegal reasons. If there is a sale or merger of the company, division or business unit that operates this site, we may also transfer the information we have collected in connection with such sale or merger.

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

SoftwareSituation.com will never collect or maintain information on our website from anyone known to be under the age of 18, and nothing on our website is specifically designed to attract anyone under 18.

## Links To Third Party Websites

We are not responsible for the privacy policies on websites that you may link to from our site. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may be different from ours. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

## Prices and Availability

The prices and the availability of our products are subject to change at any time. SoftwareSituation has the right to cancel and refund any order at our discretion. If your credit card has already been charged we will reverse the charge immediately or issue a refund to the credit card for the full amount of the purchase.

## Typographical Errors

SoftwareSituation reserves the right to refuse or cancel any order in the event of an incorrectly listed product due to typographical errors.

SoftwareSituation.com is not responsible for incorrectly submitted customer information including email. Please ensure all of your customer information is correct before submitting your order.

## Images

Images are provided for illustrative purpose only and do not necessarily indicate the actual appearance of the product. Please refer to the packaging description or call us if you have any questions.

Microsoft design/logos are registered trademarks or trademarks of the Microsoft group of companies. All other brand names, product names, or trademarks belong to their respective holders.

## Changes To This Privacy Statement

At our discretion, our privacy policy may change. If it does change, it will be for the benefit of our customers.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, you may contact us at customerservice@softwaresituation.com.

100% Genuine Software. Licenses are perpetual/permanent unless otherwise noted as a subscription.

## Installation Guarantee

SoftwareSituation.com is pleased to offer a full Installation Guarantee!

If we can't get the program you ordered from us installed, you'll get your money back!

[**_Email_**](mailto:customerservice@softwaresituation.com) or call us at **(888) 246-8519** if you need help with product installation. Product return and activation status verification is required.

## Returns

SoftwareSituation.com will exchange, refund, or credit merchandise returns made within 30 days of the ship date of the product subject to manufacturer's policies.

Each return is credited in the same manner as payment. Returns are only accepted with a Return Merchandise Authorization. Packages without the proper RMA number will not be accepted for return or refund.

All returns are subject to a 10% restocking fee and a return shipping fee.

**Downloads are non-refundable.** Please ensure you are ordering the correct product for your computer, e.g. pc or mac, 64/32 bit ect. Please contact customer service if you have any questions.

Shipped products are eligible for return, exchange, refund, or merchandise credit, within 30 days of purchase date. Shipped products must be returned in the original and unopened packaging. Please contact us for return instructions prior to returning your product. All returns are examined to insure they were not tampered with in any manner. In the unlikely situation that defective product was shipped we will gladly replace it or refund your order at our own cost.

## Need to Request a Product or Merchandise Return?

Please email [**_customerservice@softwaresituation.com_**](mailto:returns@softwaresituation.com)

**Provide the following information:**

  * Customer Name
  * Order Number
  * SKU number and quantity of the returning items
  * Indicate if the product box has been opened
  * Indicate if the product has been installed and/or activated
  * Nature of the problem with the product

A SoftwareSituation.com team member will respond to your request shortly.

SoftwareSituation.com ships within the continental United States, Hawaii, and Alaska.

## Shipping Cut Off Time

Most orders placed before 1:00pm MST will be shipped the same day the order was placed.

Orders placed Saturday, Sunday, or on a holiday will be shipped the next business day.

## Shipping to Alaska and Hawaii

Orders shipped to Alaska and Hawaii will be sent using FedEx Ground Service at an additional cost.

## Shipping Methods

SoftwareSituation.com is pleased to announce three different shipping methods.

Please note: estimated delivery is from date of order shipped.

**Priority Mail Estimated Delivery:** 2 - 3 business days

**Priority Mail Express Estimated Delivery:** 1 business day when placed before 10:00AM MST

Shipping costs will be calculated at checkout.

## Downloaded Orders

Downloaded orders usually take about 1 hour to process during business hours. Downloads are processed 7:30AM - 5:00PM MST Monday through Friday. Once the transaction is verified, your product will be sent out to you via email by one of our team members.

OEM stands for Original Equipment Manufacturer. OEM items are brand new, but they're meant for experienced users and system builders. They don't come with retail packaging, accessories or manuals, although documentation and software can typically be downloaded from the manufacturer's website.

## OEM Software is Non-Refundable

OEM items come sealed in a plain box or plastic sleeve packaging with little to no documents or instructions. Since there is no retail packaging to hide the serial number or key code, we cannot allow refunds for OEM products.

## Who Can Use OEM Software?

OEM software is intended for system builders only and cannot be transferred to another PC once it is installed. Purchasers of this software are required to comply with the terms of the System Builder License, including responsibility for providing all end-user support.

SoftwareSituation.com is not responsible for system or software incompatibility, and incompatibility issues do not qualify software as damaged or defective. Please ensure you are ordering the correct product for your computer.

## OEM Terms

Use of OEM System Builder Channel software is subject to the terms of the Microsoft OEM System Builder License. This software is intended for pre-installation on a new personal computer for resale. OEM System Builder Channel software requires the assembler to provide end user support for the Windows software and cannot be transferred to another computer once it is installed.

SoftwareSituation.com only sells genuine, new, original software that activates with the manufacturer. We do not sell used, copied, or trial software. It is your responsibility to install OEM software correctly. The manufacturer does not support OEM installations or SoftwareSituation.com for OEM installations.

Our new Reward Point Program makes it very simple to earn rewards on your purchases on our website. You will earn reward points for making purchases, referring friends, and leaving reviews. You must have a registered account with our website and be logged in to receive reward points.

Registering accounts with our website is simple and free. Click [here](https://www.softwaresituation.com/index.php?l=account) to register an account and start earning points now!

## Earning Reward Points

You can do the following to earn reward points:

  * **Making Purchases:** every time you make a purchase, you will earn reward points based on the price of the products purchased. Once your order is fulfilled, you will see the reward points added to your account on the My Account page.
  * **Referring Friends:** every time you refer a friend to place an order on our website, you and your friend will receive 500 reward points.*
  * **Company Reviews:** earn 500 reward points for leaving a review on our company review page.**
  * **Product Reviews:** earn 100 reward points for leaving a review on our products.***

## Reward Points Value

  * For every $1 spent with us here at SoftwareSituation.com, you will receive 1 reward point.****
  * Every reward point is worth 1 cent. For example, 100 reward points is equivalent to $1.00

## Redeeming Reward Points

Reward points can be redeemed at checkout on the Order Details page where you select your payment and shipping method. You can choose to redeem all or no points at any time, as long as the points reside in your bank. You must be logged in to your account to redeem your reward points. Redeemed reward points can be used in conjunction with other payment methods. Rewards cannot be combined with other promotions or discounts. Not all products are available for reward redemption.

## Products Currently Not Available For Reward Redemption

  * Microsoft Office 2013 Home and Business Full Retail PKC Box
  * Microsoft Office 2013 Home and Business Full Retail Download 1 License 1 PC

* Your referred friend must place an order with our website and use an account created with the referred email at checkout to receive the reward points. Use the Refer-A-Friend link on the My Account page once logged into your account. Limit 1 per household / company (can refer multiple friends outside of household / company).   
** You can only leave 1 company review for 500 reward points.  
*** You can only leave 2 product reviews per month for a total of 200 reward points.  
**** Reward points are calculated after any discount is applied if applicable. For Utah residents, reward points are not rewarded for sales tax.

Reward program is subject to change without notice.
